amateuralbum.net 2017-03-20

# Privacy Statement - AmateurAlbum.net

Privacy Statement  
  
Personal Information

AmateurAlbum.net allows you to visit the website without revealing any personal information about yourself. Your visit to this website is anonymous. We will only collect your contact information (first name, last name, billing address, phone number, email address and any other relevant information provided by you) as well as financial information (account or credit card numbers), with your permission and for the sole purpose of processing orders.

The information you provide will not be used for any commercial purposes and will not be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with partners who adhere to AmateurAlbum.net's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. AmateurAlbum.net may provide your personal information if necessary, in AmateurAlbum.net’s good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of AmateurAlbum.net or others.

Security Procedures and Credit Cards

In order to provide secure processing of your credit card when ordering, AmateurAlbum.net uses Secure Server Software (SSL) that is among the best in use today by e-commerce Web sites. Your personal information, including sensitive credit card information, is encrypted so that it is indecipherable by others as it travels across the Internet. 

No credit card data is stored in AmateurAlbum.net's Customer Database

. All individual contact information provided to AmateurAlbum.net is stored in secure facilities.

Cookies

Cookies are identifiers that a web site can send to your browser to keep on your computer in order to facilitate your next visit to the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many web sites use them. AmateurAlbum.net does not use cookies that persist on your hard-drive. We do use dynamic, non-intrusive session cookies, which reside in your browser's memory only for the duration of your user session, to assist in the ordering and purchasing process. AmateurAlbum.net also uses data collected through session cookies for the purpose of identifying the source of traffic (which ad or link you used to reach us), and general patterns of activity on our site. No personally identifiable information is stored in this cookie. AmateurAlbum.net uses this data to better understand what services and support is valuable to our customers, and how we can continue to provide the best online experience possible to our users.

Links to Other Sites

Our site provides links to external web sites. AmateurAlbum.net does not monitor or control the content of such web sites or whether such web sites collect or process your personal data. When you click on one of those links, you leave our site and enter one that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible. AmateurAlbum.net assumes no liability whatsoever for any kind of material available at such sites and recommends that you review their separate privacy policies.

Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using the web site or any services provided through the web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. AmateurAlbum.net may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on this Website. Your continued use of AmateurAlbum.net Software or acceptance of our e-mails following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of these changes.

Support

AmateurAlbum.net provides email support for users who purchase the software at our Helpdesk. AmateurAlbum.net does not currently provide telephone support. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, please [contact Us]() through email. We will do our best to respond to your inquiry within four business days.  
  
Horny amateurs on cam. Come and play right now!   
| 

HD

[ mrjacksonsplayroom](https://chaturbate.com/affiliates/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=mrjacksonsplayroom) 28

  * SPRING BREAK GONE WILD! Meet CupCake we meet her on the beach today! double BJ! @100 | bra off@65 | panties off@85 Tip in order from 1 to 100. Next tip: 46 #seqwithgroup

  * 98 mins, 5991 viewers

| 

HD

[ mila_](https://chaturbate.com/affiliates/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=mila_) 99

  * Sip of Grape Juice 100 tokens | My Highest Tip tonight is INFERNO with 10000 tokens

  * 113 mins, 4108 viewers

| 

HD

[ ezra](https://chaturbate.com/affiliates/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=ezra) 21

  * ♥ #lovense on♥ chillin' bc parents are home :( meow - video sale 1000 tks for 16 solo vids - 1500 tks for all b/g vids - 2500 for all videos #lovense

  * 93 mins, 3178 viewers

| 

HD

[ rosie_grey](https://chaturbate.com/affiliates/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=rosie_grey) 18

  * Parents are home... Daddy train my tight ass please #anal # submissive #tight [747 tokens remaining]

  * 98 mins, 2329 viewers

| 

HD

[ aubrilee](https://chaturbate.com/affiliates/in/?tour=LQps&campaign=jc77L&track=default&room=aubrilee) 18

  * Hit the goal 100x for squirt show! [39 tokens remaining]

  * 152 mins, 2387 viewers

---|---|---|---|---
